It’s up to viewers to decide the fate of these poor souls
trying to survive the wrath of The Undertaker.
Escape the Undertaker is a horror, mystery, family film directed by Ben Simms.
The Undertaker has set a trap for the decorated tag
team The New Day at his mansion.
What they don't know: The Undertaker's mansion is an extreme Haunted
House, packed to the brim with supernatural challenges.
It's up to viewers to decide the fate of these poor souls
trying to survive the wrath of The Undertaker.
The Undertaker, played by Mark Calaway.
Kofi Kingston, played by Kofi Sarkodie-Mensah.
Xavier Woods, played by Austin Watson.
Big E, played by Ettore Ewen.
Mark William Calaway (born March 24, 1965), better known by his ring name
the Undertaker, is an American retired professional wrestler.
He is signed to WWE, where he is a brand ambassador and a writer for
its sister promotion Lucha Libre AAA Worldwide (AAA).
Widely regarded as one of the greatest professional wrestlers of all time, Calaway spent the vast
majority of his career wrestling for WWE and in 2022 was inducted into the WWE Hall of Fame.
Calaway began his career in 1987, working under various gimmicks for World Class
Championship Wrestling (WCCW) and other affiliate promotions.
He signed with World Championship Wrestling (WCW) in 1989 for a brief stint, and
then joined the World Wrestling Federation (WWF, now WWE) in 1990.
Calaway rebranded himself as "The Undertaker" when he joined the WWF.
As one of WWE's most high-profile and enduring characters, The Undertaker is famed for his funerary themeing around an undead, macabre "Deadman" persona, which
gained significant mainstream popularity and won him the Wrestling Observer Newsletter award for Best Gimmick a record-setting 5 years in a row.
He is the longest-tenured wrestler in company history at 30 years.
In 2000, the Undertaker adopted a biker identity nicknamed "American Badass".
Calaway resurrected the Deadman gimmick in 2004, with residual
elements of the "American Badass" remaining.
The Undertaker was known for his role in WWE's flagship event WrestleMania.
He achieved 21 consecutive victories at
WrestleMania, referred to in WWE as The Streak.
He headlined the event five times (13, 24, 26, 33, and 36 – Night 1).
He is also known for pairing with his in-storyline half-brother Kane, with whom he
alternatively feuded and teamed (as the Brothers of Destruction) from 1997 through 2020.
During his wrestling career under the Undertaker gimmick, Calaway won the WWF/E Championship four times, the World
Heavyweight Championship three times, the Hardcore Championship once and the World Tag Team Championship six times.
He also won the Royal Rumble match in 2007.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.